Hi guys, I just thought this looked interesting, so let me check it out.
It says, when seeing this video cannot be unseen, it might have some interesting secrets
for us.
On the screen, this should be interesting.
I like this channel, it's called Shattered Paradise, but let's have a look at it.
Or are there others out there noticing the same pattern?
Let me show you something real quick.
The Paris Olympics opening ceremony embodies a distinctly French sensibility.
The Mona Lisa, arguably the most famous woman in art history.
But what if she wasn't a woman at all?
The widely accepted theory is that the painting depicts Lisa del Chacondo, the wife of a wealthy
Florentine merchant.
But some scholars propose another possibility for the identity of the Mona Lisa model,
Gian Giacomo Caprotti, known as Salai, Leonardo's apprentice and long-time companion.
Salai lived with Da Vinci for over 20 years and is widely believed to have been his lover.
Soleil also posed for several of Leonardo's paintings, including Saint John the Baptist,
which shows the same soft androgynous features seen in the Mona Lisa.
In 2016, researcher Silvana Vincetti used infrared scans to highlight the similarities
between Soleil's known portraits and the Mona Lisa's nose, smile and forehead.
Similar to Mona Lisa, another French artistic representation of a woman renowned for her beauty,
It's the Statue of Liberty and yes, Lady Liberty with her chiseled jawline, muscular arms and
androgynous features is also said to have been modeled after a man.
Lady Liberty might be a man.
Is Lady Liberty actually a man?
You look at the Statue of Liberty, that's not a woman.
That's a dude.
The sculptor who created the statue
may have used his brother as his model
rather than his mother as is commonly believed.
Wow, beauty is truly in the eye of a holder.
And since we're on the subject of liberty,
Let's see what the man they call the leader of the free world has to say on the subject since he recently
Expressed his thoughts on women's beauty. Who's attractive and who's not and a heated social media ran
Can I ask you a question? How much do you spend on grocers per week?
Crazy Candice Owens, who accuses the highly respected First Lady of France of being a man when she is not and will hopefully win lots of money in the ongoing lawsuit.
Actually, to me, the First Lady of France is a far more beautiful woman than Candice. In fact, it's not even close.
In fact, it's not even close. Not even close.
such a pretty face such a pretty face he said it's not even close
hmm beauty is truly in the eye to beholder now as odd as this might seem it's all very predictable
you know you're really beautiful and a woman that looks like that it's just another part of the
occult social engineering we've all been exposed to since we were little children take for instance
Oh, you dirty boy, you, oh, oh.
Take for instance, this slap, since we were little.
Usually, I play the female loving trance.
The provocative cross-dressing bunny is a symbol.
Shall we dance?
And here is looking at the ear.
It's not polite to stare.
Uh-huh, then conversely, some men need to be hit back.
Oh, it's home in one more time.
Oh my god, what was that?
Thank you President Trump, this week there was a video on board a plane that showed the
first lady of France slapping her husband Emmanuel Macron.
Do you have any world leader to world leader marital advice?
For instance, because the reggaeton artist, Bad Bunny, is known for cross-dressing and
Trump's response to bad money Super Bowl halftime performance was totally predictable.
Bad Bunny's Apple Music halftime show ripped apart by Donald Trump on Truth Social as quote,
one of the worst ever.
The president taking offense to Benito's Spanish writing, nobody understands a word
this guy is saying.
The Grammy winner's Spanish language performance, which Trump labels a slap in the face to our
country, was a celebration of America, which Trump labels a slap in the face to which Trump
labels a slap in the face.
And it doesn't look as great at the beginning, and then they'll look at by the time they
see it many, many times, it becomes the most of, they can't take their eyes off it.
performed in front of a public audience, this is likely a ritualistic demonstration of dominance
and humiliation designed to communicate a secret power dynamic.
Tonight we're looking into a story getting a lot of buzz.
It claims the Department of Justice redacted the face of the Mona Lisa in the Epstein files.
And that is certainly what this looks like.
Here is the image in question.
As you can see, the woman's face on the iconic painting has been covered with a black box.
Because of the multitude of the hordoms of the well-favored harlot, the mistress of witchcrafts.
that selleth nations through her hordoms and families through her witchcrafts.
Behold, I am against thee, said the Lord of Hosts,
and I will discover thy skirts upon thy face,
and I will show the nations thy nakedness and the kingdoms thy shame."
I just found something in the Epstein files that literally no one is talking about.
It's an email from a man named Robert Trivers who is an evolutionary biologist to Jeffrey Epstein and in this email
The unredacted version of the document in question actually does contain an image of a victim's face
Overlaid on the face of Mona Lisa
Enjoy, okay. Have a good night. I'll see you later. I'll see you on another panel. Love you